this day in 1991 that Irish musician Sinead O'Connor, it's been seven days, became the first
artist in history to refuse a Grammy Award opposing the Gulf War and the music industry's
false and destructive materialistic values. Accepting things from the establishments that
hold things up that you claim not to support. It's like Cap wanting to go back to the NFL.
Like baby them, them people have shown that they are terrible people. I know you love football but
you got to find another way to play baby. When y'all are anti-capitalist, when y'all are anti-racist
and then y'all show up to these racist capitalist spaces and you accept their awards and you cry
and you praise God and you exult. I know that for many people, what you're saying is, oh my gosh,
I am so glad that these people are finally paying me my just due for the amount of work I've put into
my craft. But like, who are these people? Because do you really think that the voting is fair? I know
in 2026, the year of the old gods and the new, we not still thinking that these spaces that are run by
actual duplicitous, nefarious people are actually fair. At the same token, you're in a room with
people who are like named in the Epstein files, who are turning a cheek on a regular basis to genocide.
But the whole existence of the award shows in the United States have been for the sake of racism,
for the advancement of Zionism, of capitalism, etc. And the work and the art that folks make so often
is being used as a tool to advance these initiatives. Think of how jazz musicians were used by the CIA
to advance the destruction of Congo's independence and the assassination of Patrice Lumumba.
So I implore you all to not only lift up the late great Sinead O'Connor, but to consider the fact that
you have the ability to follow in her footsteps and in this great time of great awakening,
to do what she did on a whole other level.
The whole liberation of oppressed people in the United States had to do not with climbing up some
ladder to success, not for asking to be just like Rockefeller or just like DuPont or just like Ford,
because that would only continue the oppression and exploitation of oppressed people in the United
States and specifically African people born and raised in the United States.